Guide to the Daily Worker and the Daily World Negatives Collection PHOTOS.223.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: 4 x 5, 120 and 127 Negatives
  - Man Pointing to Furniture Water Damage at the Apartment of [Nick Rochini?]., Jul 30, 1944; cuid37512 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00493-01 - 00493-02)
  - Mayor and General Drum, in Front of City Hall (New York, New York) and U.S. Airmail Planes., Summer 1944; cuid37513 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00494-01 - 00494-03)
  - Ambijian Committee U.S.A. Receiving Singer Sewing Machines for the Children of Stalingrad., Aug 1944; cuid37514 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00495-01 - 00495-04)
  - Home-Movie Distributor, Poster., Aug 1944; cuid37515 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00496-01 - 00496-06)
  - ["Test Shots Made Using New Short Film, New Graphics." Images Include: woman at a typewriter; large cylinders or barrels on sidewalk; copy of photographic prints of (homeless people?) lying on sidewalk or street; woman using an Addressograph machine; darkroom (the Daily Worker's?); office interior]., Aug 1944; cuid37516 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00497-01 - 00497-07)
  - [UCDVO?] Collecting Cans for Food Donations. (Sign reads: "Join the Women's Land Army".) (Bronx, New York)., Sep 1944; cuid37517 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00498-01 - 00498-05)
  - Registration for Permits to Work for High Schools., Sep 1944; cuid37518 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00499-01 - 00499-07)
  - Bronx American Labor Party Distributing Leaflets to Register for November Elections, ([170 St. Grand Concourse?] Bronx, New York)., Sep 1944; cuid37519 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00500-01 - 00500-02)
  - Picture of Man in Uniform. 35 Missions. (feature story)., Sep 1944; cuid37520 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00501-01 - 00501-02)
  - Bakers Union Local 3, [Sam Burnster?]., Oct 1, 1944; cuid37521 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00502-01 - 00502-03)
  - Columbus Day Parade, 5th Ave (New York, New York)., Oct 1944; cuid37522 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00503-01 - 00503-12)
  - Italian Women Rallying for Roosevelt, Irving Plaza (New York, New York)., Oct 1944; cuid37523 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00504-01 - 00504-04)
  - Test Shots, Taken Around East 12th and University Place (New York, New York)., Oct 1944; cuid37524 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00504A-01 - 00504A-18)
  - East Side Scenes to Illustrate (Avenue A and E. 15th St., New York, New York). L. Mitchell Story., Nov 1944; cuid37525 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00505-01 - 00505-05)
  - Unidentified Man (feature story)., 1944; cuid37526 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00506-01)
  - Permutit Company Strike, Local 475 Picket United Electrical, Radio & Machine Workers of America (UE). (Picket sign address reads: 160 Montague Street, Brooklyn, New York)., 1944; cuid37527 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00506A-01 - 00506A-02)
  - Angela Davis As A Baby and Child In Nursery School., 1944 - 1947; cuid37528 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00506B-01 - 00506B-03)
  - National Jewish Council for Russian War Relief Receiving Clothes for Neshwitzer Society to be Shipped to Neshwiz, Russia., Jan 1945; cuid37529 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00507-01 - 00507-04)
  - Installation of Officers, Harlem Society., Jan 1945; cuid37530 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00508-01 - 00508-04)
  - United Electrical, Radio & Machine Workers of America (UE) Local 450 Farewell Party to Frank Silvia, Going to the Navy., Jan 1945; cuid37531 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00509-01 - 00509-13)
  - Mrs. Alma Illery, African American leader., Jan 1945; cuid37532 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00510-01 - 00510-02)
  - Ladies Garment Center, American Labor Party Give Cans of Milk to Italy. American Relief for Italy., Feb 1945; cuid37533 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00511-01 - 00511-03)
  - National Jewish Council for Russian War Relief, Commodore Sergiev, Soviet Navy Portrait., Feb 1945; cuid37534 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00512-01 - 00512-03)
  - Radio Marine School for Veterans (feature story)., Feb 1945; cuid37535 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00513-01 - 00513-08)
  - United Office and Professional Workers of America Local 1 Making Kits for Valentine's Day., Feb 1945; cuid37536 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00514-01 - 00514-03)
  - United Electrical, Radio & Machine Workers of America (UE) Local 450 Mass Meeting, "Victory Over Fascism," Hotel Diplomat (New York, New York)., Feb 1945; cuid37537 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00515-01 - 00515-09)
  - Wounded Soldier [Mit.?] Weiner, Veteran of Two Wars., Feb 1945; cuid37538 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00516-01 - 00516-03)
  - Esther Dimkin, Stewardess on Ship (feature story)., Feb 1945; cuid37539 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00517-04 - 00517-03)
  - Colonel-Lieutenant Maurice's Daughter in House Looking at and Holding Her Father's Picture., Feb 1945; cuid37540 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00518-01 - 00518-04)
  - Officers and Members of United Office and Professional Workers of America Prior to the Convention, St. George Hotel., Feb 28, 1945; cuid37541 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00519-01 - 00519-03)
  - Jewish Trade Union Conference., Mar 1945; cuid37542 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00520-01 - 00520-04)
  - Midtown War Price Board Distributing Copies of Office of Price Administration Manual to Women Volunteers., Mar 1945; cuid37543 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00521-01 - 00521-05)
  - Congress of Industrial Organizations, Industrial Union Council of New York Introducing New Members from Amalgamated Clothing Union., Mar 1945; cuid37544 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00522-01 - 00522-02)
  - Women Setting Type Using Graphotype Machine., Mar 1945; cuid37545 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00523-01 - 00523-08)
  - Meltonian for Suede Shoe Polish from African American Discrimination Story., Mar 1945; cuid37546 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00524-01 - 00524-02)
  - Benjamin Davis and Editor of P.W. [D.W.?] in his Office., Apr 1945; cuid37547 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00525-01 - 00525-02)
  - War Emergency Court in Session, Office of Price Administration Hearing., Apr 1945; cuid37548 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00526-01 - 00526-02)
  - African American Baseball Players Getting a Tryout., Apr 1945; cuid37549 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00527-01 - 00527-05)
  - Daily Life of a Family from the Bronx - Family Time With Mother and Children, Mother Participating in Office of Price Administration Meeting (feature story)., Apr 1945; cuid37550 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00528-01 - 00528-14)
  - Mrs. Fay Pastorino of Astoria, Queens, Wife of C.I.O. Member with Three Children., Apr 1945; cuid37551 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00529-01 - 00529-03)
  - Ready for Action Stage Group Performing Before National Maritime Union Meeting, Manhattan Center, New York City., Apr 1945; cuid37552 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00530-01 - 00530-12)
  - Harry Rapaport, Veteran News Dealer At His Newstand on 14th Street and 4th Avenue (New York, New York)., Apr 1945; cuid37553 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00531-01 - 00531-02)
  - National Maritime Union Member Selling Goods to Be Sent for Members of the Seaman's Union U.S.S.R., Apr 1945; cuid37554 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00532-01 - 00532-03)
  - American Prisoners of War Return Home, Posing at Press Interview., Apr 1945; cuid37555 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00533-01 - 00533-06)
  - Scenes of Parents and Daughter With Grandfather at B&T(?) Bar and Grill., Apr 1945; cuid37556 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00534-01 - 00534-08)
  - Memorial Day Ceremonies at Soldiers and Sailors Monument, Riverside Park, New York City., May 1945; cuid37557 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00535-01 - 00535-08)
  - Local 450 United Electrical Radio and Machine Workers (UE) Membership Meeting., May 1945; cuid37558 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00536-01 - 00536-10)
  - Jewish Council for Russian War Relief Food Collection Drive for U.S.S.R in Brownsville, Brooklyn., Jun 1945; cuid37559 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00537-01 - 00537-04)
  - Wilhemina F. Adams in Her Flower Shop., May 1945; cuid37560 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00538-01 - 00538-04)
  - Sound Truck Announcing May 31st Madison Square Garden Rally, Salute to Council of Soviet American Relations (New York, New York)., May 1945; cuid37561 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00538A-01 - 00538A-04)
  - Man Posing in His Soldier's Uniform., Jun 1945; cuid37562 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00539-01 - 00539-02)
  - Conference of the Arts, Sciences and Professions in the Post-War World at Waldorf-Astoria Hotel, New York City., Jun 1945; cuid37563 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00540-01 - 00540-04)
  - Lester and Bruno (B&T Bar and Grill)., Jun 1945; cuid37564 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00541-01 - 00541-04)
  - United Electrical Radio and Machine Workers (UE) Local 450 Mass Membership Meeting, Manhattan Center, New York City., Jul 1945; cuid37565 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00542-01 - 00542-11)
  - United Electrical Radio and Machine Workers (UE) Local 450 Close-ups of Officers. Any union with [Famer?] organizations now on furlough from the army., Jul 1945; cuid37566 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00542A-01 - 00542A-10)
  - National Council of American-Soviet Friendship Greet the Soviet Representative Amidst An Exhibition of Paintings., Jul 1945; cuid37567 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00543-01 - 00543-05)
  - Anti-Franco Demonstration and Rally at Spanish Consulate, New York City., Jul 1945; cuid37568 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00544-01 - 00544-06)
  - Rube Schafer after Trip to Washington, D.C. to Cover Brankin Story., Jul 1945; cuid37569 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00545-01 - 00545-02)
  - Ladies' Purses., Jul 1945; cuid37570 (Box 4b, Shoot-negative 00546-01 - 00546-06)
  - Copies of Nazi Propaganda Pamphlets., Aug 1945; cuid37571 (Box 4c, Shoot-negative 00547-01 - 00547-04)
  - National Maritime Union Mother and Child in Their Apartment., Aug 1945; cuid37572 (Box 4c, Shoot-negative 00548-01 - 00548-02)
  - National Maritime Union Members Picket for 55 Cents an Hour Pay Increase., Aug 1945; cuid37573 (Box 4c, Shoot-negative 00549-01 - 00549-03)
  - Francis in the Office of National Maritime Union Pilot., Aug 1945; cuid37574 (Box 4c, Shoot-negative 00552-01 - 00552-02)
  - National Maritime Union Exhibit of Paintings at A.C.A. Galleries, New York City., Aug 1945; cuid37575 (Box 4c, Shoot-negative 00550-01 - 00550-04)
  - African American Women, Infirmary Discharge of Former War Workers in Government Employment Agency., Aug 1945; cuid37576 (Box 4c, Shoot-negative 00551-01 - 00551-11)
  - Local 450 United Electrical Radio and Machine Workers (UE) Mass Meeting on Layoffs, Manhattan Center (New York, New York)., Aug 1945; cuid37577 (Box 4c, Shoot-negative 00553-01 -00553-03)
  - Mrs. [Katherine Gomez?], Story on U.S. Employment Office., Aug 1945; cuid37578 (Box 4c, Shoot-negative 00554-01)
  - Community Meeting on Job Crisis, Garden City (New York)., Aug 1945; cuid37579 (Box 4c, Shoot-negative 00555-01 - 00555-10)
  - Soviet American Council Relations, Book Store in the Office., Aug 1945; cuid37580 (Box 4c, Shoot-negative 00556-01 - 00556-02)
  - John T. Smith at [Bar?] and in Front of Board of Education Bureau of Plant Operation and Maintenance. (Probably a musician, holding trumpet in negative 00558-01)., Aug 1945; cuid37581 (Box 4c, Shoot-negative 00557-01 - 00557-05)
  - Jane Cooley and Clarice [Gratman?], Story on Jim Crow Eviction., Aug 1945; cuid37582 (Box 4c, Shoot-negative 00558-01 - 00558-04)
  - The Family of Private [Charnill?] Jones in Their Yonkers Apartment., Aug 1945; cuid37583 (Box 4c, Shoot-negative 00559-01 - 00559-03)
  - Child Albert Patersen in Harlem Hospital, Visit By His Mother., Sep 1945; cuid37584 (Box 4c, Shoot-negative 00560-01 - 00560-02)
  - Madison Square Garden Rally on Spain to Salute Spanish Republic., Sep 1945; cuid37585 (Box 4c, Shoot-negative 00561-01 - 00561-14)
  - Local 450 United Electrical Radio and Machine Workers (UE) Farm Dance at ["Lost Rachochian Hall"]., Sep 1945; cuid37586 (Box 4c, Shoot-negative 00562-01 - 00562-08)
  - African Americans and Whites Work Together. (feature story)., Sep 1945; cuid37587 (Box 4c, Shoot-negative 00563-01 - 00563-07)
  - Portrait of [Harry?] Wallach., Sep 1945; cuid37588 (Box 4c, Shoot-negative 00563A-01 - 00563A-02)
  - National Maritime Union Members Registering for Leaflet Distribution for the Striking Longshoremen., Oct 1945; cuid37589 (Box 4c, Shoot-negative 00564-01 - 00564-02)
  - Benjamin Davis Election Committee., Oct 1945; cuid37590 (Box 4c, Shoot-negative 00565-01 - 00565-02)
  - Rehearsal for Benjamin Davis Ball., Oct 1945; cuid37591 (Box 4c, Shoot-negative 00566-01 - 00566-02)
  - Manhattan Office International Workers Order Welcomes the [Best Bock?] Brigades Who Collect the Most Money., Oct 1945; cuid37592 (Box 4c, Shoot-negative 00567-01 - 00567-05)
  - The Navy Yard Workers Transportation Congestion, Refurbishing [Farm?] Work (feature story)., Oct 1945; cuid37593 (Box 4c, Shoot-negative 00568-01 - 00568-02)
  - Striking Students, African American and White, Benjamin Franklin High School, 116th St. East Side, at E. 115 Pleasant Ave (Harlem, New York, New York)., Oct 1945; cuid37594 (Box 4c, Shoot-negative 00569-01 - 00569-07)
  - United Electrical Radio and Machine Workers (UE) District Convention, Two Delegates from Pittsburgh Holding UE News Publication in Laps., Nov 1945; cuid37595 (Box 4c, Shoot-negative 00570-01 - 00570-02)
  - Voting Machine Sample., Nov 1945; cuid37596 (Box 4c, Shoot-negative 00571-01 - 00571-04)
  - Veterans Picketing the Daily News, Holding Picket Signs That Read: "The News is 100% Anti-Jew, Anti-Negro, Anti-Alien, Anti-American," "Hitler Isn't Dead, He's Writing For the News, See O'Donnell's Column" and "Dust O'Donnell"., Nov 1945; cuid37597 (Box 4c, Shoot-negative 00572-01 - 00572-02)
  - Rank and File Committee International Longshoremen's Association, American Federation of Labor Picketing Outside New York Central Building [later Helmsley Building]., Nov 1945; cuid37598 (Box 4c, Shoot-negative 00573-01)
  - National Maritime Union Strikes, Office Staff of NMU Collecting Food for the United Auto Workers Strikers., Dec 1945; cuid37599 (Box 4c, Shoot-negative 00574-01 - 00574-03)
  - Bunk Johnson New Orleans Jazz Band (feature story)., Dec 1945; cuid37600 (Box 4c, Shoot-negative 00575-01 - 00575-06)
  - Picketers Protest Closing of United States Government Fair Employment Practice Committee (New York Regional Office)., Dec 1945; cuid37601 (Box 4c, Shoot-negative 00576-01 - 00576-09)
  - Table of Wage-Brackets and Tax Witholdings., Dec 1945; cuid37602 (Box 4c, Shoot-negative 00577-01 - 00577-04)
  - New York Congress of Industrial Organizations Holding a Rally to Support National Maritime Union, Manhattan Center (New York, New York). (Banner reads: "Speed our GI's Home, Get Out of China, Every Ship a Troopship")., Dec 1945; cuid37603 (Box 4c, Shoot-negative 00578-01 - 00578-08)
  - Promotion Department Photos., Dec 1945; cuid37604 (Box 4c, Shoot-negative 00579-01 - 00579-02)
  - Eugene [and Botsky?], Veterans. [Portrait of one man, though orignal caption indicates two]., Dec 1945; cuid37605 (Box 4c, Shoot-negative 00580-01 - 00580-02)
  - National Maritime Union Ship's Library., Dec 1945; cuid37606 (Box 4c, Shoot-negative 00581-01 - 00581-02)
  - National Maritime Union War Shipping Administration Stoppage to Bring GI's Home., Dec 1945; cuid37607 (Box 4c, Shoot-negative 00582-01 - 00582-11)
  - Drawing of Fred Ellis by Bill Gropper., 1945; cuid37608 (Box 4c, Shoot-negative 00583-01)
  - Miss Albena., Jan 1946; cuid37609 (Box 4c, Shoot-negative 00584-01 - 00584-03)
  - Ruth [Wernick?] and [Morris?] Nicholes, Western Union Strikers (feature story)., Jan 1946; cuid37610 (Box 4c, Shoot-negative 00585-01 - 00585-05)
  - Freeport Shooting Case (Freeport GI Slayings)., Jan 1946; cuid37611 (Box 4c, Shoot-negative 00586-01 - 00586-31)
  - Associated Food Stores Give Food to the General Motors Strikers. Mr. Percy M. Brown., Jan 1946; cuid37612 (Box 4c, Shoot-negative 00587-01 - 00587-04)
  - Jewish Council for Russian War Relief, Copy of Maksim Gorky and Sholem Aleichem., Jan 1946; cuid37613 (Box 4c, Shoot-negative 00588-01 - 00588-02)
  - Box with 25 Pounds of Sugar Cubes from Revere Sugar Refinery Going to U.S.S.R. Story by Harry Raymond., Jan 1946; cuid37614 (Box 4c, Shoot-negative 00589-01 - 00589-05)
  - Congress of Industrial Organizations Demonstrate for Western Union Strikers., Feb 1946; cuid37615 (Box 4c, Shoot-negative 00590-01 - 00590-06)
  - Copies of Photographs of 1919 Steel Strikes in Pennsylvania, for Howard., Feb 1946; cuid37616 (Box 4c, Shoot-negative 00591-01 - 00591-02)
  - Greek Organization Demonstrating In Front of British Consulate Against British Occupancy in Greece., Feb 1946; cuid37617 (Box 4c, Shoot-negative 00592-01 - 00592-04)
  - Jewish Council for Russian War Relief Meeting at Hotel Pennsylvania (New York, New York)., Feb 1946; cuid37618 (Box 4c, Shoot-negative 00593-01 - 00593-09)
  - Mildred Linsley, Executive Director of "Stage for Action"., Feb 1946; cuid37619 (Box 4c, Shoot-negative 00594-01 - 00594-02)
  - Johannes Steel, American Labor Party Demonstrating with Petitions, Leaders of Delegation to the Board of Education for May Quinn's Dismissal., Feb 1946; cuid37620 (Box 4c, Shoot-negative 00595-01 - 00595-04)
  - Manhattan District International Workers Order Receiving Stations and Rewarding the Best Show Members., Mar 1946; cuid37621 (Box 4d, Shoot-negative 00596-01 - 00596-09)
  - Veterans of World War II in Magistrate Court., Mar 1946; cuid37622 (Box 4d, Shoot-negative 00597-01 - 00597-03)
  - Jim [Allen?], Daily Worker Columnist., Mar 1946; cuid37623 (Box 4d, Shoot-negative 00598-01 - 00598-02)
  - Women's Reception in the Soviet Consulate for the International Women's Day., Mar 1946; cuid37624 (Box 4d, Shoot-negative 00599-01 - 00599-04)
  - War Veterans Picket the Real Estate Board Offices. (Picket signs read: "Put Teeth on the Patman Housing Bill," "Lobbies Against Veterans Housing" and "Restore Subsidies and Price Ceilings to Patman Bill")., Mar 1946; cuid37625 (Box 4d, Shoot-negative 00600-01 - 00600-07)
  - Best's Department New Building Construction and Housing Shortage Story, Tishman Realty and Construction Company., Mar 1946; cuid37626 (Box 4d, Shoot-negative 00601-01 - 00601-07)
  - Lucky Strike Strikers Getting Ready for Their Broadcast., Mar 1946; cuid37627 (Box 4d, Shoot-negative 00602-01 - 00602-02)
  - Union Square Rally, Protest Freeport Shooting and Tory Churchill, Speeches. (Signs include: "Attack on Negro Veterans is Attack on All Veterans," and "We Veterans Demand Justice in Freeport")., Mar 1946; cuid37628 (Box 4d, Shoot-negative 00603-01 - 00603-09)
  - Protest Picket Demonstration in Front of Waldorf Astoria Against Tory Churchill. (Picket signs include: "The British People Reject Churchill As Do We" and "Tory Churchill Wants War, We Don't".) (New York, New York)., Mar 1946; cuid37629 (Box 4d, Shoot-negative 00604-01- 00604-15)
  - Rally Against May Quinn, City Hall Protest by Parents' Association and Women's Auxiliary National Maritime Union. (Picket signs Include "Teach Democracy Not Fascism" and "Mayor O'Dwyer Said: There's no room for a bigot in our schools")., Mar 1946; cuid37630 (Box 4d, Shoot-negative 00605-01 - 00605-07)
  - 6th Ave and 14th Street Butcher Shop Story. People from Harlem Coming to Buy Meat (New York, New York)., Mar 1946; cuid37631 (Box 4d, Shoot-negative 00606-01 - 00606-03)
  - Copies of Sim [José Luis REY-VILA] Paintings from Spain for [Laulin?]., Apr 1946; cuid37632 (Box 4d, Shoot-negative 00607-01 - 00607-04)
  - Milk Story, Photos Taken in the Grocery. (Feature story by Luise)., Apr 1946; cuid37633 (Box 4d, Shoot-negative 00608-01 - 00608-03)
  - International Union of Painters and Allied Trades, District Council 9, Signing Insurance Bill in Mayor's Office., Apr 1946; cuid37634 (Box 4d, Shoot-negative 00609-01)
  - Paintings for Howard, Daily Worker., Apr 1946; cuid37635 (Box 4d, Shoot-negative 00614-01 - 00614-03)
  - Mr. Miller, Passover Ceremonies in the House., Apr 1946; cuid37636 (Box 4d, Shoot-negative 00610-01 - 00610-03)
  - Communist Party U.S.A. Union Square Rally for Office of Price Administration. (Picket signs include "We Demand of the Senate, Stop the Raid on O.P.A.")., Apr 1946; cuid37637 (Box 4d, Shoot-negative 00611-01 - 00611-13)
  - Librarian and Employees at Library on Convent Avenue, New York, New York (feature story by Lola)., Apr 1946; cuid37638 (Box 4d, Shoot-negative 00612-01 - 00612-03)
  - Packers' Union Convention., Apr 1946; cuid37639 (Box 4d, Shoot-negative 00613-01 - 00613-06)
  - National Negro Congress, Mr. [Dowli(n)g?] and Ms. Rebel., Apr 1946; cuid37640 (Box 4d, Shoot-negative 00615-01 - 00615-04)
  - Puppets for Congress of Industrial Organizations (feature story)., Apr 1946; cuid37641 (Box 4d, Shoot-negative 00615 -01A - 00615-02A)
  - Jewish Council for Russian War Relief for Odessa Relief, Meeting and Presentation at Hotel Capitol (New York, New York)., May 1946; cuid37642 (Box 4d, Shoot-negative 00616-01 - 00616-06)
  - Jewish Council for Russian War Relief for Katinka and Chotinar Relief, Meeting and Presentation at Webster Hall, New York, New York., May 1946; cuid37643 (Box 4d, Shoot-negative 00617-01 - 00617-08)
  - Jewish Council for Russian War Relief, 5th National Convention at Hotel Astoria (New York, New York). (Banner reads: "Firm Friendship and Cooperation between USA and USSR for World Peace")., May 1946; cuid37644 (Box 4d, Shoot-negative 00618-01 - 00618-20)
  - Women's Page Daily Worker, Preparation of an Eggplant., May 1946; cuid37645 (Box 4d, Shoot-negative 00619-01 - 00619-02)
  - Copy of Potsdam Conference Picture (seated from left to right, Clement Attlee, Harry S. Truman, Joseph Stalin)., May 1946; cuid37646 (Box 4d, Shoot-negative 00620-01 - 00620-02)
  - Louis Weinstock's Brother Just Arrived From Germany [Occupied Bratislava?]., May 1946; cuid37647 (Box 4d, Shoot-negative 00621-01 - 00621-02)
  - Kings County American Labor Party Office of Price Administration Rally, Borough Hall, Brooklyn (New York). [Banner reads "Save O.P.A."]., May 1946; cuid37648 (Box 4d, Shoot-negative 00622-01 - 00622-05)
  - Railroad Stoppage, Scenes in Grand Central Station (New York, New York)., May 1946; cuid37649 (Box 4d, Shoot-negative 00623-01 - 00623-08)
  - Harlem Interracial Nursery, Feature Story., May 1946; cuid37650 (Box 4d, Shoot-negative 00624-01 - 00624-17)
  - Jim [Conoly?/Cowdy?], New York City Councilman in His Office with Letters Received on His Bill., May 1946; cuid37651 (Box 4d, Shoot-negative 00625-01 - 00625-02)
  - Furriers, Copies of Pictures for 1946 Convention and Rally, International Fur and Leather Workers Union., May 1946; cuid37652 (Box 4d, Shoot-negative 00626-01 - 00626-16)
  - United Nations Relief and Rehabilitation Administration (UNRA), Greek Seamen in the U.S.A., May 1946; cuid37653 (Box 4d, Shoot-negative 00627-01 - 00627-03)
  - Maxine Wood., May 1946; cuid37654 (Box 4d, Shoot-negative 00628-01 - 00628-03)
  - Delegation of Negro Organization in Albany, Demonstration on the Freeport Case., May 1946; cuid37655 (Box 4d, Shoot-negative 00629-01- 00629-02)
  - Two Jewish Veterans from German Concentration Camps arriving in New York., May 1946; cuid37656 (Box 4d, Shoot-negative 00630-01 - 00630-02)
  - Sales Tax Hearing - Council Chambers, City Hall (New York, New York)., May 1946; cuid37657 (Box 4d, Shoot-negative 00631-01 - 00631-13)
  - 42nd Street Art Exhibition and Book Store. TH [Tribune?]., May 1946; cuid37658 (Box 4d, Shoot-negative 00632-01 - 00632-02)
  - Farewell Party Given to Novick at [Souen?/ Soubren?/Southern?] Restaurant and Bar., May 1946; cuid37659 (Box 4d, Shoot-negative 00633-01 - 00633-07)
  - Yugoslav Committee Opening of Greater New York Collection Campaign In Front of United States Treasury. By [Homer?] Governor. Legman and Ben Collins., May 1946; cuid37660 (Box 4d, Shoot-negative 00634-01 - 00634-07)
  - Cloak Finishers Branch 409 and Jewish People's Fraternal Order of the International Workers Order Unveiling a Tombstone (of Aaron Nudelman) on (Harry) Nudelman Grove [Grave?]. International Workers Order Cemetery., May 1946; cuid37661 (Box 4d, Shoot-negative 00635-01 - 00635-16)